karooya.com 2018-08-14

# Privacy Policy - Karooya

* ##### GENERAL INTRODUCTION

This Privacy Policy (together with our website's Terms of Use and any additional data privacy notices on our website or in targeted e-mails) explains how KAROOYA collects, uses the data of our website visitors/ client/ business contacts and the circumstances under which we may disclose such information to others. 

This Privacy Policy is effective from July 17, 2014. Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page. 

The primary purpose of KAROOYA's website is to be a dynamic resource, business tool and offer specified online Services. We believe in maintaining your privacy while creating valuable, robust websites, giving you the best user experience possible, and providing you with customized services and information. 

We want you to feel secure when visiting our website and are committed to maintaining your privacy when doing so and therefore we implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your information. 

While subscribing to our Services or registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name; email; address, phone number or credit card information. Pages that collect this type of information may provide further information as to why your data is needed and how it will be used. It is completely up to you whether you want to provide it or not. 

You may also visit our website anonymously. 

* ##### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USAGE

**_What information do we gather?_**

KAROOYA may collect and process the following information: 

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website. This includes registering to use the website, placing an order, subscribing to services, newsletters and alerts etc. 
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 
  * We may ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to necessarily respond to them. 
  * Any postings, comments or other content that you upload or post to KAROOYA website. 
  * Our website collects information about your computer, including (where available) your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration, to filter traffic, to look up user domains and to report on statistics. 
  * Details of your visits to our website, the pages you view and resources you access or download, including but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data). 

**_How do we use information that we collect from the site?_**

  * **To personalize your experience**  
_Your information helps us to better respond to your specific needs_

  * **To improve our website**  
_We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you_

  * **To improve customer service**  
_Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests & support needs_

  * **To process transactions**  
_Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any third party for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested._

  * **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**

  * **To send periodic emails**  
_The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc._  
_Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email._

In a nutshell, we use your data to perform our obligations for the Services you have subscribed to; information you request, and for other similar purposes which we would describe to you at the point where it is collected or which will be obvious to you. 

We also analyze your IP and browser information to determine what is most effective about our website, to help us identify ways to improve it and make it more effective. 

**_Will we share your information with outside parties?_**

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your information. 

We generally only share your information with our contracted service providers and advisors who assist us in operating our website, conducting our website or business, or servicing you, so long as these parties agree to be bound by confidentiality obligations. 

However, there will be other times when we need to share or disclose the information you provide for a specific purpose, for example: 

  * In the case we are running a joint event and have informed you that the information will be shared with our partners. But again, we will notify you as to why we are asking for specific information and it is completely up to you whether you want to provide it or not; 
  * We may need to disclose your information to third parties in the event that we sell or liquidate any part of our business or assets; 
  * We will disclose or share your information to comply with any legal obligation, or to enforce or apply our Terms of Use; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of KAROOYA, our clients, or others. 

However, non personal/non identifiable visitor information may be provided to third parties for marketing, advertising or similar other purposes. 

* ##### INFORMATION PROTECTION

**_How do we protect your information?_**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. We use a secure server. All information (sensitive or otherwise) is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer(SSL) Technology. The credit card information is encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems and who are bound by confidentiality obligation. 

However, you should understand that the open nature of the Internet is such that information may flow over networks connecting you to our systems without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended. 

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the sites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these sites, please note that these sites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or sites. Please check these policies before you submit any information to these sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**_What are your rights?_**

You are entitled to know whether we hold information about you and, if we do, to have access to that information and require it to be corrected if it is inaccurate. You can do this by contacting us through the channel provided below. 

You can exercise your right to prevent marketing communications to you by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your personal information, or by utilizing opt-out mechanisms in e- mails we send to you. You can also exercise the right to discontinue marketing communications to you, or to have your information removed from our customer relationship management (CRM) databases at any time by sending us email on the address provided below. 

**_Have a question or complaint?_**

If you can't find what you're looking for here, or have a concern about our Privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below: 

* ##### MARKETING

KAROOYA uses information of clients, customers and other business contacts in various ways to develop and strengthen client and business relationships, provide information about Company, services, publications and communicate about and market our services. 

The following describes use of your information for marketing purposes: 

**Sources of Marketing Data.** The bulk of the information we collect and use for marketing purposes relates to individuals; employees or authorised agents of our clients and other companies with which we have an existing business relationship. We may also obtain contact information from public sources, including content made public at social media websites, to make an initial contact with a relevant individual or company. 

**Targeted E-mail.** We send commercial e-mail to individuals; employees or authorised agents of our client or other companies with whom we want to develop or maintain a business relationship. Our targeted e-mail messages typically include web beacons, cookies, and similar technologies that allow us to know whether you open, read, or delete the message, and links you may click. When you click a link in a marketing e-mail you receive from KAROOYA, we will also use a cookie to log what pages you view and what content you download from our websites, even if you are not registered at or signed into our site. 

**Combining Data from Multiple Sources.** As described above, we may combine data from publicly available sources, and from our e-mail, website, and personal interactions with you. We combine this data to better understand your needs, to assess the suitability of our service offerings for your needs, and to perform the other activities described throughout this Privacy Policy. 

* ##### RECRUITING

If you use KAROOYA's online career resources, we collect information that you submit to the website and use it for recruiting-related purposes. We may also use the same technologies we use for Marketing to provide job seekers with a personalized online experience, to send relevant information about careers and opportunities at KAROOYA, and to analyze the effectiveness of our recruitment efforts and resources. 

_The terms and conditions along with privacy policy with all references, constitutes the sole and entire agreement of the parties to this agreement with respect to the subject matter contained herein, and supersedes all prior terms and conditions._
